Finding aid to Amnesty International's Country Dossiers, Europe, Albania to Estonia.
IDC Publishers
- Estonia, 15
  - General AI material / Background papers, E
    - Estonia: The death penalty; homosexuality; conscientious objection to military service., 12/1992; Amnesty International's Concerns in Europe May 1992 - October 1992.; (EUR 01/04/92); E5 (Microfiche 134)
    - SURAN 21/92 - Republic of Estonia: Talyschanov (first name not known)., 9/9/1992; (EUR 51/02/92); E6 (Microfiche 134)
    - Estonia., 1 January 1993; The Baltic States: Time to abolish the death penalty (EUR 06/01/93)..; E7 (Microfiche 151)
    - Estonia: Countries which abolished the death penalty in 1998., 1 May 1999; The Death Penalty Worldwide: Developments in 1998.; (ACT 50/04/99); E7 (Microfiche 264)
    - Estonia., 8 March 1993; Medical letter writing action: The death penalty in the Baltic States.; (EUR 06/03/93); E8 (Microfiche 151)
    - Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003., 1 October 2003; (EUR 01/016/03); E8 (Microfiche 350)
    - Republic of Estonia: Ruben Melkonjan., 25 March 1993; (EUR 51/04/93); E9 (Microfiche 151)
    - Estonia., 1 October 2003; Concerns in Europe and Central Asia January - June 2003.; (EUR 01/016/03); E9 (Microfiche 350)
    - Estonia., 1 April 1993; Baltic States: Amnesty International launches campaign against death penalty.; (Weekly Update Service 20/93, NWS 11/20/93); E10 (Microfiche 151)
    - Estonia:, 4 October 2004; Belarus and Uzbekistan: The Last Executioners: The trend towards abolition in the former Soviet space.; (EUR 04/09/04); E10 (Microfiche 375)
    - Republic of Estonia: Vladimir Botchko., 7 April 1993; (EUR 51/05/93); E11 (Microfiche 151)
    - Estonia., 1 December 2005; Europe Central Asia: Summary of Amnesty International's Concerns in the Region: January - June 2005.; (EUR 01/012/2005); E11 (Microfiche 399)
    - Estonia: The death penalty; Amnesty International calls for investigation into prison deaths., 1 June 1993; Concerns in Europe November 1992 - April 1993.; (EUR 01/01/93); E12 (Microfiche 152)
    - Republic of Estonia: Vassili Otshtalenko., 1 November 1993; (EUR 51/08/93); E13 (Microfiche 152)
    - Nos. 14-15 not used., E14
    - Estonia: Work for legislative change., 1 January 1994; Violations of the rights of homosexuals: extracts from Amnesty International action materials.; (POL 30/01/94); E16 (Microfiche 170)
    - Estonia: The death penalty; ratifications., 1 January 1994; Concerns in Europe May - October 1993.; (EUR 01/01/94); E17 (Microfiche 170)
    - Republic of Estonia: Sergei Krylov., 12 April 1994; (EUR 51/01/94); E18 (Microfiche 170)
    - Estonia: The death penalty., 1 June 1994; Concerns in Europe November 1993 - April 1994.; (EUR 01/02/94); E19 (Microfiche 170)
    - Estonia: Death in custody; the detention of asylum-seekers; conscientious objection to military service., 1 February 1995; Concerns in Europe May-December 1994.; (EUR 01/01/95); E20 (Microfiche 187)
    - Estonia: The detention of asylum-seekers; conscientious objection to military service., 1 September 1995; Concerns in Europe January-June 1995.; (EUR 01/02/95); E21 (Microfiche 187)
    - Estonia: Amnesty International's concerns on the death penalty., 1 September 1995; (EUR 51/01/95); E22 (Microfiche 187)
    - Estonia: Ratifications., 1 August 1996; Concerns in Europe January - June 1996.; (EUR 01/02/96); E23 (Microfiche 207)
    - Estonia., 1 August 1996; The Baltic States: A summary of recent concerns.; (EUR 06/01/96); E24 (Microfiche 207)
    - Estonia: The alleged ill-treatment of David Mease and Erkki Maasalo., 23 September 1996; (EUR 51/02/96); E25 (Microfiche 208)
    - Estonia., 1 March 1997; Concerns in Europe July - December 1996.; (EUR 01/01/97); E26 (Microfiche 226)
    - Estonia: Moves towards abolition., 1 June 1997; The death penalty worldwide: developments in 1996.; (ACT 50/05/97); E27 (Microfiche 226)
    - Estonia: The death penalty; Asylum-seekers., 1 September 1997; Concerns in Europe January - June 1997.; (EUR 01/06/97); E28 (Microfiche 226)
    - Azerbaijan and Estonia abolish the death penalty., 26 March 1998; Death Penalty News March 1998.; (ACT 53/02/98); E29 (Microfiche 245)
    - Estonia., 1 April 1998; The death penalty worldwide: Developments in 1997.; (ACT 50/04/98); E30 (Microfiche 245)
    - Estonia: The death penalty; ratifications., 1 September 1998; Concerns in Europe January-June 1998.; (EUR 01/02/98); E31 (Microfiche 245)